ourlads.com 2006-05-10

# 2006 NFL Draft - 2006 NFL Mock Draft from Ourlads Scouting Services

**Online Privacy Policy**

OURLADS' Scouting ServicesTM (also referred to in this document as OurladsTM) is in the business of information collection and analysis, and we know how important privacy is to you. Because of our interest in protecting your privacy, our company and its affiliates have adopted the following privacy principles to underscore our commitment to valued subscribers of our services.

**1.** We recognize that you expect privacy and security in your affairs. We understand the need to safeguard sensitive information about you that you have entrusted to us. We maintain standards and procedures, including our Deletion Policy, designed to avoid misuses of information. 

**2.** We collect, retain, and use information about you only where we reasonably believe that it will help us administer our business or provide products and services to you. We collect and retain information only for specific business purposes, after which, in accordance with our Deletion Policy, that information is removed from our business records. 

**3.** We have procedures to help ensure that information about you is accurate, current, and complete in accordance with commercial standards. We will respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccurate or incomplete information. 

**4.** We limit employee access to information to employees with a business reason to know that information. Our employees understand the importance of confidentiality, and we take appropriate steps to assure the integrity of the information we collect. 

**5.** We do not reveal specific information about our customers to parties outside of our corporation. It is for our independent use and will be disclosed only if you authorize it or the disclosure is otherwise lawfully permitted or required. 

**6.** With the exception of one page, the Individual Newsletter page, we do not use "cookies." The use of cookies on the Individual Newsletter page is not to collect general data from those who order from this page, but merely to keep track of what newsletter orders have been placed in a customer's virtual "shopping cart." No personal data is stored at all. These cookies are set up so that they expire the following day. 

**7.** We employ 128-bit, Secure Systems Layer (SSL) encryption technology for online purchases of Ourlads publications. Confirmation of the security of online transactions on the Ourlads website can be determined through the presence of a security certificate, also known as a Digital ID, issued by VeriSignTM. (Read VeriSign's Secure Server White Paper for more information about e-commerce security.) 

**8.** While not restricting access to this website from minors, it is the policy of Ourlads not to accept purchase orders from minors, nor to collect personally identifiable information from them. If you have submitted personal information and would like it removed or modified, or if your child has submitted personal information that you would like to request be removed, please contact us at: 

**1-800-PRO-DRAFT**
